<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hackhathon on Mehmet Ozan Ünal</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/tags/hackhathon/</link><description>Recent content in hackhathon on Mehmet Ozan Ünal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2014–2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 18:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mozanunal.com/tags/hackhathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[TR] Hackhathon Getir 2018</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/2018/04/getir-hackhathon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 18:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mozanunal.com/2018/04/getir-hackhathon/</guid><description>It is a project developed for BiTaksi Getir Hackathon 2018. Detailed information can be found from below.
Team Paketci! Check our app from here which is deployed using heroku.
Check github repo of app from here
Getir Hackhathon 2018 Team Members: Sertan Sezgin Kutlu Ertuğrul Çınar Mehmet Ozan Ünal
Paketci App Its a work on pack collection and delivery for courier and observer.
Features: By Backend: 1.Assign routes for couries by relate most efficent path.</description></item><item><title>[TR] Hash Code 2018</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/2018/04/hash-code-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mozanunal.com/2018/04/hash-code-2018/</guid><description>Herkese Merhabalar, Hash Code Google tarafından dünya çapında düzenlenen bir algoritma yarışmasıdır. Bu yıl itibariyle son 3 tanesine ben de katılmış bulunuyorum. Hatta geçen sene yarışma hakkında bir yazı da yazmıştım. Bu geleneği bu yıl da devam ettirmeye karar verdım.
Bu seneki yarışmada çok başarılı olamadık derece anlamında. Ama yarışmada çalışan, puan alabilen bir çözüm sunmak bile baya zor. O nedenle ben de çözümüzü birazcık açıklamak istiyorum. Aşağıdan direk github reposunu inceleyebilirsiniz.</description></item><item><title>Artwork Sharing Platform with Augmented Reality</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/2017/04/art-sharing-platform-1521976119976/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 18:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mozanunal.com/2017/04/art-sharing-platform-1521976119976/</guid><description>This is a project develop for Tech4Culture Hackhathon 2017.
Project features:
You can share artworks You can follow artist who you like You can explore and experience artworks with augmented reality You can follow art foundations for art and culture activities Future Improvements
Supporting artist about scanning and sharing of their artworks. Expanding supported artworks for augmented reality ( showing performing art as animation) _NOP Team Mehmet Ozan Unal Ali Sivgin Ertugrul Cinar</description></item></channel></rss>