<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raspberry Pi Laptop on Mehmet Ozan Ünal</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/tags/raspberry-pi-laptop/</link><description>Recent content in Raspberry Pi Laptop on Mehmet Ozan Ünal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2014–2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 01:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mozanunal.com/tags/raspberry-pi-laptop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DIY Raspberry Pi Laptop</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/2015/10/diy-raspberry-pi-laptop-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 01:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mozanunal.com/2015/10/diy-raspberry-pi-laptop-16/</guid><description>Hi,
In this article, DIY Raspberry Pi Laptop project will be told. I needed a low cost mini computer with high mobility but then i decided to make my own and i start to this project. Most of the parts(expect Raspberry pi 2 and its some of materials) were bought from china and the total cost of this project is 110$. There is video of this project under this paragraph. You can watch this then you learn how i did this project step by step.</description></item><item><title>[TR] DIY Raspberry Pi Laptop</title><link>https://mozanunal.com/2015/09/diy-raspberry-pi-laptop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mozanunal.com/2015/09/diy-raspberry-pi-laptop/</guid><description>Herkese Merhabalar,
Bu yazımda Raspberry Pi 2 kartını kullanarak kendim için yaptığım laptop projesinden bahsetmek istiyorum. Kendime düşük maliyetli gündelik işlerimi halletmek için taşınabilir bir bilgisayar almaya karar vermiştim fakat neden kendim yapmak yerine satın alayım dedim ve bu projeye başladım. Malzemelerin çoğunu yurt dışından aldım ve bana toplam maliyeti 110$ kadar oldu.
Projemin tanıtım videosunu izleyebilirsiniz. Yazının devamında ise Raspberry Pi laptopun yapılışını adım adım öğrenebilirsiniz.
[![](https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-32Tefe5cxxQ/VfQJVHRLDKI/AAAAAAAANq0/a35hSfl8s2s/s320/IMG_20150912_123948.jpg)](https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-32Tefe5cxxQ/VfQJVHRLDKI/AAAAAAAANq0/a35hSfl8s2s/s1600/IMG_20150912_123948.jpg) 1. Raspberry Pi Nedir?</description></item></channel></rss>